Wilyza Yap

With a background in psychology, I'm a passionate UX researcher based in California. My journey is anchored in an appreciation for technology and a fascination with the human mind. By blending my psychological insights with user experiment research, I uncover deep-rooted user behaviors and preferences, translating them into thoughtful and intuitive digital designs. My mission is to bridge the gap between human psychology and technology, creating user-centric solutions that resonate and elevate the digital landscape.

1320 Graymill Court Rohnert Park, California, 94928 (707) 318-9713 wilyzayap@gmail.com

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

California State University East Bay — Lab assistance

August 2023-present

Collected Data exploring the questions among neurodiverse individuals and with the data created data-analysis plans.

SKILLS

Figma

Miro

SPSS and JASP

DESIGN THINKING

RESEARCH

User Interviews

Heuristic evaluations

Personas

INSIGHT IMPLEMENTATION

Storyboards

Concept mapping

Sketches

USABILITY TESTING

Guerilla testing

Card sorting

A/B Testing

PROTOTYPING

Wireframes

Cliable lo/mid/high fidelity

Mock-ups

OTHER WORK EXPERIENCE

CERTIFIED NURSE ASSISTANT (CNA)

Record and report care of patients

August 2019- September 2022

EDUCATION

California State University East Bay - Psychology BA

August 2022-August 2023

Completion of GPA: 3.4

Santa Rosa Junior College - Associates

August 2017- May 2020

Transfer GPA 3.7

UC Berkeley Extension

April 2023- October 2023

Certification in Ux/UI Design

PROJECTS

Redesign for a non-profit website

A week week group project that focuses on designing a website for a non-profit organization. We conducted user research, sketching, wireframes, and testing.